

Nguyen Ba Nhat

Web Developer

nguyenbanhat1907@gmail.com

0367273177

OBJECTIVE

I'm not only a Wordpress developer but also Frontend and Backend developer having approximately 3 years of experience in this field. I always want to apply my knowledge and experience to contribute to the development of the company and improve my ability.

My CV online: https://koolboy1907.github.io/

WORK EXPERIENCE

BONSEY JADEN

MAR 2018 - MAR 2019

WEB DEVELOPER (WORDPRESS, ANGULAR 4 + NODE JS, FRONTEND, LARAVEL, SHOPIFY)

Starting new project

Dwell (Wordpress): https://dwellstudent.com

- Coding UI from file design
- Building theme and function for other page

Shaves2U (Angular 4 + Node JS): https://shaves2u.com

- Responsive and fix bug UI website
- Coding Angular 4 to manage content admin and checkout process shopping.
- Coding Node JS create API to process database

Prutopia (Handlebars view engine + Node JS): https://shaves2u.com

- Use view engine create UI and mange content admin website
- Coding Node JS create API to process database

Chivas (Laravel): https://successisablend.sq

Nutrafol auiz (Laravel): https://nutrafolquiz.testing.ws

- Coding UI from file design
- Building template and coding function for other page

Teatulia bar(Shopify):https://teatuliabar.com

- Coding UI from file design
- Customize theme Shopify and coding function for other page

Nutro(UI): http://nutro.asia/

Yonex(UI): https://vcore.yonex.com/

- Just need to build static website, coding UI from file design

3S INTERSOFT JSC

DEC 2016 - DEC 2017

WEB DEVELOPER (WORDPRESS, YII2, JOOMLA)

1. Be assigned maintain projects

Nissan (Joomla): http://nissan-techvn.com

- Manage content website
- Communicate directly with customers

Crisis (Yii2): https://crisis.vn

- Fix bug and update module by coding

Value partner (wordpress): https://www.valuepartners-group.com

- Fix bug and create new function from customer's requirement
- Communicate directly with customers
- Performance Optimization
- Deploy to server

2. Starting with new project

System Square System (wordpress): http://www.systemsquare.co.jp **Vung Tau Land (wordpress)**: http://muabannhadatvungtau.net

- Analysis Requirement
- Coding
- Execute Unit Test
- Fix bug and maintain
- Communicate directly with customers
- Deploy to server

WEB DEVELOPER (FRONTEND, DRUPAL)

- Building the website based on Drupal CMS and responsive webdesign.
- Create design and technical solutions.
- Communicate directly to client for discussions and requirements.
- Create and execute project work plans and revises as appropriate tomeet changing needs andrequirements.
- Starting from code Front-end to Back-end when necessary.
- Complete some projects with maintenance and fix bug frequent.

Link projects:

http://infinitypups.net

http://www.ukfitnessevents.co.uk

http://www.sunrisesolarmd.com

http://vmxpo.com

FREELANCER (PERSONAL)

2018 - NOW

WEB DEVELOPER (WORDPRESS)

Link projects:

http://thuctinhtra.com

https://nhadatmoinhat.net

EDUCATION

VIETTECHKEY COMPANY

DEC 2015 - MAR 2016

FRONTEND + WORDPRESS

nternship

- Use photoshop to design, make UI website by file PSD, cut layoutfrom file PSD to buid file HTML.
- Use CorelDraw to draw, design logo.
- Experience about HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery and some externallibraries.
- Knowledgeable and good use Css Prepocessor (SASS, LESS), be

CESOFT

APR 2016 - NOV 2016

ableto use Git, Koala, Nodejs, Bower, Grunt.

- Knowledgeable about Bootstrap and Responsive for many screensuch as mobile, tablet, desktopand larger.
- Knowledgeable about PHP and Wordpress platform, OOP coding,MVC.
- Experience with MySQL, database design, query profiling, WooCommerce.

DA NANG UNIVERSITY - SCIENCE & TECHNOLOGY

SEP 2010 - FEB 2016

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Student

SKILLS

Angular, Node JS

Photoshop

Teamwork

Communication

English

INTERESTS

- Technology
- Game
- Music
- Sport & Gym

Wordpress	
PHP/SQL	_
HTML/CSS	
Javascript/Jquery	
Lavavel, Yii2, Shopify	
Joomla, Drupal	